A Guide to the Correspondence Files of Special Collections, University of Virginia Library 1931-1990s
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series I: Correspondence (General)
  - Manuscripts Department Correspondence [ante 1990] and Patron-Use Files (Box A28-7A through A29-17T)
    - Jones, Charles Pinckney (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones Family Ledgers (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, John Beauchamp (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, John Page (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, John Paul (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, Maryus (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, Walter (MSS #8557) (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, William A. (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones, Wilhemina (Box A28-13T)
    - Jones Memorial Library (Box A28-13T)
    - Jordan, Conrad Baxter (Box A28-13T)
    - Jordan, Joseph A., Jr. (Box A28-13T)
    - Journal of Southern History (Box A28-13T)
    - Jouett, Jack (Box A28-13T)
    - Joyce, James (Box A28-13T)
    - Joynes, Edward (Box A28-13T)
    - Junkin Family (Box A28-13T)
    - K misc. 1930-1989 (Box A28-14A)
    - Kanawha Valley, WV (Box A28-14B)
    - Kasson, John Adam (Box A28-14B)
    - Kean Family Papers (Box A28-14B)
    - Kean, Jefferson Randolph (see also Jefferson - Manuscripts - Kean) (Box A28-14B)
    - Kean, Robert G. (Box A28-14B)
    - Kean, Robert H. (Box A28-14B)
    - Keats (Box A28-14B)
    - Keeley, Mary P. (Box A28-14B)
    - Kekocton Baptist Association (Box A28-14B)
    - Kellar, Herbert A. (Box A28-14B)
    - Kelly, Mrs. John J. (Box A28-14B)
    - Kemper, James Lawson (Box A28-14B)
    - Kemper Papers (Box A28-14B)
    - Kendall, Paul (Box A28-14B)
    - Kendig, Perry F. (Box A28-14B)
    - Kennedy, John F. (Box A28-14B)
    - Kennedy, John Pendleton (Box A28-14B)
    - Kenner, Hugh (Box A28-14B)
    - Kennan Institute (Box A28-14B)
    - Kennon Papers (Box A28-14B)
    - Kent, UK (Box A28-14B)
    - Kentucky (Box A28-14C)
    - Kentucky Historical Society Register Index (Box A28-14C)
    - Kentucky, University of (Box A28-14C)
    - Kepner, William A. (MSS #4538-f) (Box A28-14C)
    - Kerlan, Irwin (Box A28-14C)
    - Ker-Porter Papers (Box A28-14C)
    - Key, Francis Scott (Box A28-14C)
    - Keyes, Frances Parkinson (Mrs. Henry Keyes) (Box A28-14C)
    - Keys (Box A28-14C)
    - Kilner, Kenton (Box A28-14C)
    - Kilpatrick, James Jackson (Box A28-14C)
    - Kilpatrick Column - Indexing Questions (Box A28-14C)
    - Kilpatrick, Jack (Box A28-14C)
    - Kimball, Fiske (Box A28-14C)
    - Kimball, Marie (Box A28-14C)
    - Kimura, Kikuya (Box A28-14C)
    - Kincaid, E.A. (Box A28-14C)
    - King, George H.S. (Box A28-14C)
    - King, Grace (Box A28-14D)
    - King, Mrs. W.W. (Box A28-14D)
    - Kinsolving Family (Box A28-14D)
    - Kinzie, Frances Harshbarger (Box A28-14D)
    - Kipling, Rudyard (Box A28-14D)
    - Kirkland, Caroline (Box A28-14D)
    - Kisling, Dorothy (Box A28-14D)
    - Klingberg, Frank J. (Box A28-14D)
    - Knollenberg, Bernhard (Box A28-14D)
    - Knote, Dr. Theodore W. (Box A28-14D)
    - Knox, Henry (Box A28-14D)
    - Knox, John (1977- ) (Box A28-14D)
    - Kocher, A. Lawrence (Box A28-14D)
    - Kohler, Dayton (Box A28-14D)
    - Kohn, John S. Van E. (Box A28-14D)
    - Korda, Michael (Box A28-14D)
    - Kosciuszko - Jefferson (Box A28-14D)
    - Kosciuszko, Thaddeus (Box A28-14D)
    - Kounsler, Randolph (Box A28-14D)
    - Kraus, H.P. (Box A28-14D)
    - Kreymborg Papers (Box A28-14D)
    - L misc. 1940-1986 (Box A28-14E)
    - L misc. 1930-1939 (Box A28-14F)
    - L misc. 1985-1989 (Box A28-14F)
    - Labels - Box (Box A28-14G)
    - Labernum Library (see also Bryan) (Box A28-14G)
    - Lacy, Dan (Box A28-14G)
    - LaFarge, Father John (Box A28-14G)
    - Lafayette Papers (Box A28-14G)
    - Lafayette (see also Yorktown Campaign) (Box A28-14G)
    - Lafayette, Marquis de (Box A28-14G)
    - Lakeside Press (Box A28-14G)
    - Lamb, Mrs. Brockenbrough (Box A28-14G)
    - Lamb, Charles (Box A28-14G)
    - Lancashire County Record Office (Box A28-14G)
    - Lancaster, Dabney (Box A28-14G)
    - Land Grants (Box A28-14G)
    - Land, Robert H. (Box A28-14G)
    - Langford, Gerald (1952- ) (Box A28-14G)
    - Lankes, J.B. (Box A28-14G)
    - Latane Family Papers (Box A28-14G)
    - Latin-American Manuscripts (Box A28-14G)
    - Latrobe, Benjamin (Box A28-14G)
    - Lauck, W. Jett (Box A28-14G)
    - Lawrence, D.H. (Box A28-14H)
    - Lay, K. Edward 1987-1989 (Box A28-14H)
    - Lazear, Jesse (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee, Arthur (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee Calendar (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee, Cazenove G. (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee, Charles Carter (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee Family (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee, Fitzhugh (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee, Henry (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee, Lawrence (Box A28-14H)
    - Lee Papers - photostats at Yale (see also Photostats - Harvard) (Box A28-14I)
    - Lee - Revolutionary - Photostats at Harvard (see also Photostats - Yale) (Box A28-14I)
    - Lee, Richard Bland (Box A28-14I)
    - Lee, Richard Henry (Box A28-14I)
    - Lee, Robert E. (Box A28-14I)
    - Lee - Stratford (Box A28-14I)
    - Lefevre Attic Move (Spring 1985) (Box A28-14I)
    - Legal Instruments 1972-1988 (Box A28-14I)
    - Legal Problems - House Bill #1754 1975 (Box A28-14I)
    - Legal Problems (Box A28-14I)
    - Legare, James M. (Box A28-14I)
    - Lehmann-Haupt, Helmut (see also Bibliographical Society of America) (Box A28-14I)
    - Leigh-Hunt 1988 (Box A28-14I)
    - Leigh Family (Box A28-14I)
    - Leland, Elder John (Box A28-14I)
    - Lemonnier, Dr. Leon (Box A28-14I)
    - Leonard, Bascom - Gift (Box A28-14I)
    - Leacek Family (see also Lincoln, Abraham) (Box A28-14I)
    - Lester, Malcolm (Box A28-14I)
    - Letcher, John (Box A28-14I)
    - Leuchtenburg, William E. (Box A28-14I)
    - Leverson, Ada (Box A28-14I)
    - Levit Letters (Box A28-14I)
    - Levy Family - of Monticello (Box A28-14I)
    - Lewis, Clifford, III (Box A28-14I)
    - Lewis Family (Box A28-14J)
    - Lewis Family Papers (Box A28-14J)
    - Lewis, Margaret - Commonplace Book (Box A28-14J)
    - Lewis, Meriwether (Box A28-14J)
    - Lewis, Sinclair (Box A28-14J)
    - Lewis, Thomas (Box A28-14J)
    - Lewis and Clark Papers (Box A28-14J)
    - Lexington Presbytery (Box A28-14J)
    - Libertarian Party 1988 (Box A28-14J)
    - Libertarian Party Archives (Box A28-14J)
    - Library of Congress (Box A28-14J)
    - Library of Congress - Center for the Coordination of For. Mss. (Box A28-14J)
    - Library of Congress - Information Bulletin (Box A28-14J)
    - Library of Congress - Loan Division (Box A28-14J)
    - Library of Congress - Manuscripts Division (Box A28-14K)
    - Library of Congress - Map Division (Box A28-14K)
    - Library of Congress - Overseas Photocopying (Box A28-14K)
    - Library of Congress - Photoduplication Service (Box A28-14K)
    - Library of Congress - Rare Book Room (1952- ) (Box A28-14K)
    - (Box A28-14K)
    - Library of Congress - Sioussat, St. George L. (Box A28-14K)
    - Library of Congress - Union Catalogue 1946-1952 (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - AACR 2 Implementation Task Force (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - ALAS ALAC (Space Allocation Committee) (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - BRS (Cataloguing) (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - Bibliographic Records Services (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - Branches Technical Services (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - Collection Development (Box A28-14K)
    - Library Company of Philadelphia (Box A28-14K)
    - Library - Faculty Salary Increases - Ad Hoc Committee (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Committee on Faculty Status (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Committee on the Future of the Card Catalogue (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Committee on Library Orientation (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Committee on Locked Stacks (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Newspaper Committee (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Online Catalogue Planning Committee (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Committee on Policy for Library [Faculty] Research (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Preservation Comittee (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Preservation Committee - Minutes (Box A28-14L)
    - Library - Publications Committee 1983-1986 (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Committee on Reproduction Fees (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Committee on Safety and Emergencies (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Committee on Staff Development (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Technical Assistant Committee (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Travel Funds Policy Committee (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Report of University Library Committee (Box A28-14M)
    - Library - Goals and Objectives Committee (Box A28-14N)
    - Library Handbook (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Manuscripts Department - Minutes (Box A28-14N)
    - Library Rotation Program (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Manuscripts Department - Staff Absence Forms (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Organization Charts (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Program Groups (Boards) (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Reference Department (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Retrospective Conversion Project (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Science / Technology-Reports / Minutes (Box A28-14N)
    - Library Security Newsletter (Box A28-14N)
    - Library Self-Study (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Storage Library Collections & Access Committee (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Task Force on Catalog Usage (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Task Force on Technical Considerations & Cost (Box A28-14N)
    - Analysis (Box A28-14N)
    - Library - Task Force on Technical Processing (Box A28-14N)
    - Library of Southern Literature (Box A28-14N)
    - Lightfoot, Philip (Box A28-14O)
    - Ligon (Box A28-14O)
    - Lincoln (Box A28-14O)
    - Lindsay, N. Vachel (Box A28-14O)
    - Liston, Robert (Box A28-14O)
    - Literary Property (Box A28-14O)
    - Littlepage, Lewis (Box A28-14O)
    - Littleton, Frank C. (see also James Monroe Assoc.) (Box A28-14O)
    - Lloyd, Wildon (Box A28-14O)
    - Loans Returned 1974 (Box A28-14P)
    - Locke, John (Box A28-14P)
    - Logan Gray, Inc. (Box A28-14P)
    - Logan, Rayford (Box A28-14P)
    - Lomax, John Taylor (Box A28-14P)
    - London, Jack (Box A28-14P)
    - London, Lawrence (see also Confederate Imprints; Virginia Imprints) (Box A28-14P)
    - London, University of (Box A28-14P)
    - Long, Professor George (Box A28-14P)
    - Long, Mrs. Ralph (Box A28-14P)
    - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (Box A28-14P)
    - Lorris, S.G. (Box A28-14P)
    - Loudoun County & Historical Society (see also Balch Library) (Box A28-14P)
    - Louisa County (Box A28-14P)
    - Lousiana (Box A28-14P)
    - Louthan, Henry T. (Box A28-14P)
    - Lowdermilk, W.H. & Co. (Box A28-14P)
    - Lowell, James Russell (Box A28-14P)
    - Loans Returned 1974-1976 (Box A28-14Q)
    - Loans Returned 1979 (Box A28-14Q)
    - Loans - Correspondence re 1987 (Box A28-14R)
      Chiefly concerning interlibrary loans, but with some information on exhibition loans.
    - Loans Returned 1980-1981 (Box A28-14R)
    - Loans Returned 1985-1987 (Box A28-14R)
    - Loans - Correspondence re (Box A28-14S)
    - Loans - Correspondence re 1971-1977 (Box A28-14S)
    - Loans - Correspondence re, and Returns 1988-1989 (Box A28-14S)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - General (Box A28-14T)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - Accounts (Box A28-14T)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - Expenditures (Box A28-14T)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - Transactions (Box A28-14T)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - Summary financial (Box A28-14T)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - Processing (papers) (Box A28-14T)
    - Low Moor Iron Co./ Borderland Coal Co. Project - Budget / Payroll (Box A28-14T)
    - Lucas, Eliza (Box A28-14T)
    - Luck, Mae (Box A28-14T)
    - Lucretius (Box A28-14T)
    - Lutheran Church (Box A28-14T)
    - Lyle, Katie L. (Box A28-14T)
    - Lynch, Charles (Box A28-14T)
    - Lynch Law (Box A28-14T)
    - Lynchburg (Box A28-14T)
    - Lynchburg Foundry Company (Box A28-14T)
    - Lynchburg News and Advance (Box A28-14T)
    - Lyons Family (Box A28-14T)
    - McBryde, Stewart (Box A28-15B)
    - McCabe, William Gordon (Box A28-15B)
    - McCasland, Vernon (Box A28-15B)
    - McClary, Jane (Box A28-15B)
    - McClellan, Woodford (Box A28-15B)
    - MacClenny Papers (Box A28-15B)
    - MacClenny, W.E. (Box A28-15B)
    - McConnell, James (Box A28-15B)
    - McCormick, Charles D. (Box A28-15B)
    - McCormick Collection (Box A28-15B)
    - McCormick-Goodhart, Leander (Box A28-15B)
    - McCutchan, J. Wilson (Box A28-15B)
    - MacDonald, Edmund F. (Box A28-15B)
    - McDowell Family Papers 1986 (Box A28-15B)
    - MacDonald, James & Co. (Box A28-15C)
    - McDowell Family Papers (Box A28-15C)
    - McDowell Manuscripts (Box A28-15C)
    - McFarland, Carl / Justice Stanley F. Reed (Box A28-15C)
    - McGehee-Hawkins Papers (Box A28-15C)
    - MacGowan, Everett W. (Box A28-15C)
    - McGroarty, William B. (Box A28-15C)
    - McGregor Library (see also McGregor accessioned as MSS #11263) (Box A28-15C)
    - McGregor Fund Trustees (Box A28-15C)
    - McGuffey (Box A28-15C)
    - McGuire, Hunter Holmes (Box A28-15C)
    - Machemer, A.F. (Box A28-15C)
    - MacLeod, Mrs, John W. (Box A28-15C)
    - McIntire, Paul Goodloe (Box A28-15C)
    - MacKay, Colin B. (Box A28-15D)
    - McKay, H.B. (see also MSS #3821) (Box A28-15D)
    - MacKay-Smith, Alexander (Box A28-15D)
    - MacKenzie, Col. Alan (Box A28-15D)
    - McKnight Papers (Box A28-15D)
    - McLaws, Mrs. John T. (Box A28-15D)
    - Mc misc. 1983 (Box A28-15D)
    - Mc misc. 1986-1989 (Box A28-15D)
    - McLean, Jay (Box A28-15E)
    - MacLeish, Archibald (Box A28-15E)
    - McManaway, Dr. James G. (Box A28-15E)
    - McMath-Hulbert Observatory (Box A28-15E)
    - McMurdo, Muriel (Box A28-15E)
    - McMurtrie, Douglas C. (see also American Imprints; Mississippi) (Box A28-15E)
    - McPherson, Mrs. E.H. (Box A28-15E)
    - McPherson Papers (Box A28-15E)
    - McReynolds, James (Box A28-15E)
    - McReynolds, James Clark (Box A28-15E)
    - MacShane, Frank (Box A28-15E)
    - McVitty, Samuel Herbert (Box A28-15E)
    - McWane, Fred W. (Box A28-15F)
    - McWane, Henry E. (Box A28-15F)
    - Madden, T.O. (Box A28-15F)
    - Maddux, T.H. & Co. (Box A28-15F)
    - Madison, Dolley (Box A28-15F)
    - Madison, James 1937-1984 (Box A28-15F)
    - Madison, James - Papers of 1966-1976 (Box A28-15F)
    - Madison, Bishop James (Box A28-15F)
    - Madison Papers 1957-1965 (Box A28-15F)
    - M misc. 1923-1965 (Box A28-15G)
    - M misc. 1970-1987 (Box A28-H)
    - M misc. 1966-1969 (Box A28-15I)
    - M misc. 1988-1989 (Box A28-15I)
    - Madison, James (1985- ) (Box A28-15I)
    - Madison, James - Editorial Project (Box A28-15I)
    - Madison, James - Books (Box A28-15I)
    - Madison, James - Library (see also Scott, W.W.) (Box A28-15I)
    - Madison Letter Loss (Box A28-15I)
    - Magruder, John Bankhead (Box A28-15I)
    - Mahone Family Papers (Box A28-15J)
    - Mahone-McGill Papers (Box A28-15J)
    - Main, Mrs. Robert (Box A28-15J)
    - Mallet, John W. (Box A28-15J)
    - Mallet, Marcus (Box A28-15J)
    - Mallory Family Papers (Box A28-15J)
    - Malone, Dumas (Box A28-15J)
    - Manahan, Jack (Box A28-15J)
    - Manassas Battle (Box A28-15J)
    - Manchester Libraries (Box A28-15J)
    - Mann Genealogy (Box A28-15J)
    - Mann, Harrison (Box A28-15J)
    - Mann, Gov. William Hodges (Box A28-15J)
    - Manuscripts 1939-1950 (Box A28-15J)
    - Manuscripts - Administration of (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Applications for Employment (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Care of (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts Control (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts Division - Employment Information (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Equipment (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Guides and Union Lists (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Job Descriptions (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Loans (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Medical (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Medieval and Renaissance (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts - Policies (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts Purchased (including Jefferson Fund) (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts Division - Service Ratings (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts Division - Shelving (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscript Society, The (Box A28-15K)
    - Manuscripts Society (Box A28-15L)
    - Appendices to Self-Evaluation (Box A28-15L)
    - Manuscripts - Student Assistants (1964- ) (Box A28-15L)
    - Manuscripts - Thefts and Thieves (Box A28-15L)
    - Manuscripts Co. of Springfield (Box A28-15L)
    - Manuscripts in Virginia by R.E. Stocking (Box A28-15L)
    - Maps (see also Mann, C.H.; Doolan, J.; Fry, J.; Farrer; Crown coll.) (Box A28-15L)
    - Maps and Maps - Virginia (Box A28-15M)
    - Maps - Confederate Museum (Box A28-15M)
    - Maps - Requests for (Box A28-15M)
    - Maps - Kentucky (Box A28-15M)
    - Maps of Virginia (see also Thornton Map) (Box A28-15M)
    - Mariners Museum (Box A28-15M)
    - MARAC (see also Mid-Atlantic Regional Archives Conference) 1988 (Box A28-15M)
    - Markham, Edwin (Box A28-15M)
    - Marshall, George C., Research Library (Box A28-15M)
    - Marshall, J.J. (Box A28-15M)
    - Marshall, James Collier (Box A28-15M)
    - Marshall, John (Box A28-15M)
    - Marshall, John - Papers of (Box A28-15N)
    - Maury-Fontaine Papers 1988-1989 (Box A28-15N)
    - Marshall, R.C. (Box A28-15N)
    - Marshall, Mrs. William C. (Box A28-15N)
    - Marsteller, E.H., Jr. (Box A28-15N)
    - Martin Family (Box A28-15N)
    - Martin, Thomas S. (Box A28-15N)
    - Marvin, George (Box A28-15N)
    - Mary Ball Memorial Museum (Box A28-15N)
    - Mary Washington College (Box A28-15N)
    - Maryland (Box A28-15N)
    - Maryland Colony Charter (Box A28-15N)
    - Maryland Historical Society (Box A28-15N)
    - Maryland Imprints (see also Bristol, Roger) (Box A28-15N)
    - Maryland-Virginia-DC Regional Group of Cataloguers (Box A28-15N)
    - Mary Washington College Library (Box A28-15O)
    - Mason, Mrs. Cora (Box A28-15O)
    - Mason Family (Box A28-15O)
    - Mason, George (Box A28-15O)
    - Mason, J. Tate (Box A28-15O)
    - Mason, Robert French, III / Josephine Carswell (Box A28-15O)
    - Masonic Lodge (Box A28-15O)
    - Massachusetts Historical Society (Box A28-15O)
    - Massey, Linton (Box A28-15O)
    - Massie Family (Box A28-15O)
    - Massie, G. Edmond (Box A28-15O)
    - Massey, John (Box A28-15O)
    - Masters, Edgar Lee (Box A28-15O)
    - Masterson, William (Box A28-15P)
    - Material Sent to Other Institutions (Box A28-15P)
    - Mather, Cotton (Box A28-15P)
    - Matthews, John Carter (see also Lee, R.H.) (Box A28-15P)
    - Matthews, Johnson (Box A28-15P)
    - Maugham, Somerset (Box A28-15P)
    - Maupin Family Papers (Box A28-15P)
    - Maupin, Socrates (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury, Ann (see also Adams) (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury, James (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury, Matthew Fontaine (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury, Capt. Richard (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury Papers (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury Papers - Fontaine [Maury] 1985-1987 (Box A28-15P)
    - Maury Family (Box A28-15P)
    - Maverick, Ruth (Mrs. G.M.) (Box A28-15Q)
    - Mayes, Mrs. J.G. (Box A28-15Q)
    - Mayo, Bernard (Box A28-15Q)
    - Mayo, Frederick (Box A28-15Q)
    - Mays, David J. (Box A28-15Q)
    - Mazzei, Philip (Box A28-15Q)
    - Meacham, Harry (Box A28-15Q)
    - Meade, Alice (Box A28-15Q)
    - Meade, Everard K. (Box A28-15Q)
    - Meade, Robert Douthat 1985 (Box A28-15Q)
    - Meade Family (Box A28-15R)
    - Meade, Robert D. 1989 (Box A28-15R)
    - Meade, Robert Dothat (Box A28-15R)
    - Meade, R.D. (Box A28-15R)
    - Mearns, David C. (Box A28-15R)
    - Medicine (Box A28-15R)
    - Medieval Manuscripts (Box A28-15R)
    - Medina Centennial Celebration (Box A28-15R)
    - Meeks, Bernard M. (Box A28-15R)
    - Melville, Herman (Box A28-15R)
    - Mellon, Paul 1988-1989 (Box A28-15R)
    - Mellon, Paul 1950-1974 (Box A28-15R)
    - Memoranda - Sent by Berkeley 1968-1980 (Box A28-15R)
    - Memos 1968-1980 (Box A28-15R)
    - Memos 1982 (Box A28-15R)
    - Memos 1981 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Incoming from General Office 1982 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Incoming from University 1982 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memoranda (Old) - re: Travel (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Outgoing by EB 1982 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Outgoing 1982 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Outgoing by EB 1985 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memoranda to Manuscripts People re: Working Hours (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos 1983 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Incoming - University 1983 (Box A28-15S)
    - Memos - Incoming - General Office 1983 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos - Outgoing - EB 1983 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos - Incoming - University 1984 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos - Incoming - General Office 1984 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos - Outgoing - EB 1984 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos 1984 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos - Incoming - General Office 1985 (Box A28-15T)
    - Memos - Outgoing - EB 1986 (Box A28-16A)
    - Memos - Incoming - University 1985 (Box A28-16A)
    - Memos - Outgoing 1988-1989 (Box A28-16A)
    - Memos - Incoming - General Office 1986 (Box A28-16A)
    - Memos - Incoming - General Office 1988-1989 (Box A28-16A)
    - Memoranda - Incoming - General Office 1987 (Box A28-16B)
    - Memoranda - Incoming - General Office 1989-1990 (Box A28-16B)
    - Memoranda - Outgoing - EB 1987 (Box A28-16B)
    - Memoranda - Outgoing 1988-1990 (Box A28-16B)
    - Mencken, Henry Louis (Box A28-16C)
    - Menefee Family (Box A28-16C)
    - Mercer Family (Box A28-16C)
    - Mercer, Hugh (see also Flickinger, B. Floyd) (Box A28-16C)
    - Mercer, John (Box A28-16C)
    - Meredith Family (Box A28-16C)
    - Meredith, George (Box A28-16C)
    - Meriden Gravure Company (Box A28-16C)
    - Merrill, Boynton (Box A28-16C)
    - Meriwether Family (Box A28-16C)
    - Metcalf, John Calvin (Box A28-16C)
    - Methodist Church (Box A28-16C)
    - Mettauer, Dr. John Peter (Box A28-16C)
    - Metzdorf, Robert - Bills (Box A28-16C)
    - Metzdorf, Robert - Resume (Box A28-16C)
    - Metzdorf, Robert 1973 (Box A28-16C)
    - Metzdorf, Rober 1970 (Box A28-16C)
    - Metzdorf, Rober 1965-1969 (Box A28-16D)
    - Mewshaw, Michael (Box A28-16D)
    - Mexican War (Box A28-16D)
    - Mexico (Box A28-16D)
    - Meyer, Nicholas (Box A28-16D)
    - Michael, J. Harry (Box A28-16D)
    - Michie Family (Box A28-16D)
    - Michie Company (Box A28-16D)
    - Michie, Thomas J. (Box A28-16D)
    - Michie Tavern (Box A28-16D)
    - Michigan (Box A28-16D)
    - Micro Methods Ltd. (Box A28-16D)
    - Microfilm 1950-1952 (Box A28-16D)
    - Microfilm 1964-1984 (Box A28-16D)
    - Microfilm (1983- ) (Box A28-16D)
    - Microfilming Corp. of America (Box A28-16D)
    - Micrometers (Box A28-16E)
    - Mid-Atlantic Regional Archives Conference (see also MARC) (Box A28-16E)
    - Middleton, Arthur Pierce (see also Colonial Williamsburg) (Box A28-16E)
    - Midway Mill (Box A28-16E)
    - Milburne, Virginia S. (Box A28-16E)
    - Military History (Box A28-16E)
    - Military Service - Deferment (Box A28-16E)
    - Millay, Edna St. Vincent (Box A28-16E)
    - Millenial Harbinger (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller - Applications (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller, C.W. 1940-1951 (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller, Carl F. (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller, Col. Francis Pickins (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller, Helen Hill (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller, Henry (Box A28-16E)
    - Miller, John C. (Box A28-16F)
    - Miller, John Carl - Estate of (Box A28-16F)
    - Miller School (Box A28-16F)
    - Mills, Robert (Box A28-16F)
    - Miltmore, Dr. Dean 1950 (Box A28-16F)
    - Milton (Box A28-16F)
    - Mining (Box A28-16F)
    - Minisink Valley Historical Society (Box A28-16F)
    - Minnesota (Box A28-16F)
    - Minor, C. Venable (Box A28-16F)
    - Minor Family Papers (Box A28-16F)
    - Minor, James (Box A28-16F)
    - Minor, John Barbee (Box A28-16F)
    - Mish, Charles C. (Box A28-16G)
    - Missionaries - Asian (Box A28-16G)
    - Mississippi (Box A28-16G)